Guide to the U.S. Agency for International Development Records, Programs, and Itineraries 1960-1968
U.S. Agency for International Development Records, Programs, and Itineraries
- Leather Chemistry for Foremen, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.119
- Leather Chemistry for Foremen, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.120
- Leather Chemistry for Foremen, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.121
- Management and Supervision of a Sales Force, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.122
- Management and Supervision of Sales Force, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.123
- Management and Supervision of a Sales Force, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.124
- Personnel Management: Job Analysis, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.125
- Personnel Management: Selection and Placement of Personnel, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.126
- Personnel Management: Job Evaluation, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.127
- Personnel Management: Wage and Salary Administration, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.128
- Personnel Management: Wage and Salary Administration, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.129
- Personnel Management: wage and Salary Administration, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.130
- Personnel Management: Personnel Records and Statistics, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.131
- Advertising Principles and Problems, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.132
- Foundry Supervisory Training: Molding and Core Sands, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.136
- Foundry Supervisory Training: Cupola Design and Operation, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.137
- Foundry Supervisory Training: General Molding Practice, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.138
- Supervisory Safety Training (Box 5, Folder 51)
  Agency for International Development; Training Manual No.139
- Training Materials for the Instruction of Foundry Supervisors or Supervisory Candidates (Box 6, Folder 1)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 2
- Management Primer: Procurement and Inventory, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Training Manual No. 98
- Management Primer: Production Management, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Training Manual No. 97
- Job Instruction Training manual (Box 6, Folder 4)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 4
- Job Methods Training Manual (Box 6, Folder 5)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 5
- Supervisory Development Program (Box 6, Folder 6)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 6
- Program Development Institute (Box 6, Folder 7)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 7
- Using Job Instruction Training (Box 6, Folder 8)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 8
- Union Job Relations Training Manual (Box 6, Folder 9)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 9
- Job Relations Training Case Studies (Box 6, Folder 10)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 10
- Training Course in Material Handling (Box 6, Folder 11)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 11
- Discussion Leadership: Suggestions on the Conduct of Small Group Discussions (Box 6, Folder 12)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 12
- The Supervisory Six (Box 6, Folder 13)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 13
- New Foreman Training Plan (Box 6, Folder 14)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 14
- Selection and Training of New Foremen (Box 6, Folder 15)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 15
- Power Plant Training Course: Steam Accessories (Box 6, Folder 16)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 16
- General Operating Rules for Power Boilers (Box 6, Folder 17)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 17
- Plant Fire Brigade Training (Box 6, Folder 18)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 18
- Industrial First Aid Training (Box 6, Folder 19)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 19
- Communications in Business and Industry (Box 6, Folder 20)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 20
- Conference Leadership Training (Box 6, Folder 21)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 21
- Economics Training (Box 6, Folder 22)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 22
- Effective Job Organization, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 23
- Management Development Programs for Executives and Supervisors and Manufacturing Division, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 24
- Fundamentals of Management: Basic Supervisory Training, Training in Human Relations, Leadership Training, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 25
- Maintenance Training Program, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 26
- Problems in Business Management: Nature and Scope of Management Responsibilities (Box 6, Folder 27)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 27
- Problems in Business Management: Organization (Box 6, Folder 28)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 28
- Problems in Business Management: Human Relations (Box 6, Folder 29)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 29
- Problems in Business Management: Management Training (Box 6, Folder 30)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 30
- Problems in Business Management: Incentive Plans (Box 6, Folder 31)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 31
- Problems in Business Management: Manufacturing Costs (Box 6, Folder 32)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 32
- Problems in Business Management: Production Planning (Box 6, Folder 33)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 33
- Problems in Business Management (Box 6, Folder 34)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 34
- Problems in Business Management: Costs and Budgets (Box 6, Folder 35)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 35
- Problems in Business Management: Business Leadership (Box 6, Folder 36)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 36
- Industrial Training Sound Films (Box 6, Folder 37)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 38
- Management and Supervisory Training Program, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 39
- Economics Training: Charts (Box 6, Folder 39)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 40
- Operating a Fork Truck (Box 6, Folder 40)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 41
- Waste Reduction, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 42
- Lubrication Fundamentals and Practices, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 43
- Personnel Management, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 45
- Machinery Manufacturing Cost Accounting (Box 6, Folder 44)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 46
- The Responsibility of the Training Supervisor (Box 6, Folder 45)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 47
- Induction Training (Box 6, Folder 46)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 48
- Production Training (Box 6, Folder 47)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 49
- Preparation of Training Course Outlines (Box 6, Folder 48)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 50
- Departmental Personnel Procedures, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 51
- How to Select New Supervisors, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 52
- Techniques of Day-to-Day Supervisor: Performance Levels Depend on Quality of Supervision, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 53
- Selecting Management Personnel, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 54
- Memo and Report Writing, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 55
- Public Relations Training, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 56
- Industrial Training Methods (Box 6, Folder 55)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 57
- Training Course in Cost Accounting (Box 6, Folder 56)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 59
- Cost Control Accounting (Box 6, Folder 57)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 60
- Training Course in Marketing (Box 6, Folder 58)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 61
- Metal-Working Industry Training Manual (Box 6, Folder 59)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 62
- Department Store Merchandising (Box 6, Folder 60)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 63
- Record-Keeping Forms for the Handcrafter, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 64
- Retail Selling (Box 6, Folder 62)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 65
- Quality Control (Box 6, Folder 63)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 66
- Training TWI Trainers Top Management Seminars Starting a Management Association, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 67
- Production Management Methods in a Small Shop (Box 6, Folder 65)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 68
- Management's Responsibility for Supervision (Box 6, Folder 66)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 69
- Office Training (Box 6, Folder 67)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 70
- Wage Incentives, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 71
- Supervisory Training Through Individual Coaching, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 72
- Industrial Safety leader's Guide, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 73
- Industrial Safety Leader's Guide (Box 6, Folder 71)
  International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 74
- Industrial Safety Leader's Guide (Box 6, Folder 72)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No. 75
- Industrial Safety Leader's Guide, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No. 76
- Industrial Safety Leader's Guide, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No. 77
- Industrial Safety Leader's Guide, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No. 78
- Industrial Safety Guide, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No. 79